The best never rest.
RED 2 is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Dean Parisot.
Retired C.I.A.
agent Frank Moses reunites his unlikely team of elite operatives for a
global quest to track down a missing portable nuclear device.
Frank Moses, played by Bruce Willis.
Marvin Boggs, played by John Malkovich.
Sarah Ross, played by Mary-Louise Parker.
Young FBI Agent, played by Dan Jeannotte.
Bailey, played by Anthony Hopkins.
Victoria, played by Helen Mirren.
Red 2 is a 2013 American action comedy film directed by Dean Parisot and written by Jon and
Erich Hoeber, based on the comic book series Red by Warren Ellis and Cully Hamner.
It is the sequel to Red (2010).
The film stars Bruce Willis, John Malkovich, Mary-Louise Parker, Anthony Hopkins, Helen
Mirren, Catherine Zeta-Jones, Byung Hun Lee, Brian Cox, and Neal McDonough.
Red 2 premiered at the Westwood Village Theatre in Los Angeles California on July 11, 2013,
and was released in the United States on July 19, by Summit Entertainment.
The film received generally mixed reviews from critics.
A sequel was announced as in-development in 2013 but did not come to fruition.
The film explores themes of london, england, central
intelligence agency (cia), paris, france, england, europe.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.